Sadanand Badak

YOGA TEACHER

- 9326292733
- @ sadayoga77@gmail.com
- Mumbai

Profile

Passionate yoga teacher with over 3+ years of professional experience in Hatha yoga and Ashtang yoga classes. In 2019, completed an Advanced Yoga Teacher Training acquired an in depth knowledge about postures, breathing techniques, and spiritual elements of yoga teaching

Skills

Physical Skills

Leadership
Integrity

Communication

Mentoring

Creativity

Education

Masters in business economis

2019 - 2020

UNIVERSITY OF MUMBAI

Masters in yogashastra

2021 - present

K.J. SOMAIYA VIDYAVIHAR UNIVERSITY

200 HRS YOGA TTC

2021

YGI OF YOGA & NATUROPATHY, RAJASTHAN

YCB LEVEL 1-YOGA INSTRUCTOR

2021

MORARJI DESAI NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF YOGA

Work Experience

SUVI YOGA HOUSE

Yoga Teacher 2019 - 2020

- Experience of teaching yoga to more than 250 student off different age group.
- designing and leading flow of traditional and ashthanga yoga.
- · Teaching Different types of meditations.

HOUSE OF HAPPINESS, ANDHERI

Yoga Teacher

2022 - Present

 Designed yoga class sequences and integrated lesson plans, including vinyasa and flow formats for beginner and advanced students.

MOULD FITNESS, GRANT ROAD

Yoga Teacher 2022 - Present

FREELANCING

Yoga Teacher 2020 - Present

 Teaching in Private and Group yoga classes. Possess proven track record in helping clients achieve fitness goals through customized exercises programs.

Languages

- Marathi
- English
- Hindi